<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on The Galatean Saga</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on The Galatean Saga</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Behind the Scenes: The Spacer and the December Chronicles</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/behind-the-scenes-the-spacer-and-december-chronicles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 29 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/behind-the-scenes-the-spacer-and-december-chronicles/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;the-dream-that-started-everything&#34;&gt;The Dream That Started Everything&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Two years ago this December, I had a dream that changed everything.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;That dream became the seed of The Galatean Saga. Since then, I&amp;rsquo;ve written, rewritten, and built out the canon of this universe—its wars, its cadets, its fractured families, and its long shadow between Earth and Galatea. I&amp;rsquo;ve completed drafts for three novels, but I&amp;rsquo;ve learned something crucial: &lt;em&gt;writing&lt;/em&gt; the books is only the beginning. The editing, polishing, cover design, formatting—everything that goes into releasing something of real value—takes even longer than writing the drafts themselves.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Welcome to the New Galatean Saga Website</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/welcome-to-the-new-galatean-saga-website/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/welcome-to-the-new-galatean-saga-website/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;a-new-home-for-the-galatean-saga&#34;&gt;A New Home for The Galatean Saga&lt;/h2&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m excited to announce the launch of the new official website for The Galatean Saga! After years on Blogger, I&amp;rsquo;ve moved to a more flexible platform that better reflects the immersive, multi-dimensional nature of this universe.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h3 id=&#34;why-the-change&#34;&gt;Why the Change?&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;The old Blogger site served us well, but as The Galatean Saga has grown from a single book concept into a multimedia storytelling experiment—spanning novels, music, video, and interactive experiences—I needed a space that could evolve with it.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
